Guide to the New-York Historical Society Pictorial Archive 1804-2000 (bulk 1930-1960) NYHS 5
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Exhibits, 1932-2000
  - ART what thou EAT: Images of Food in American Art, 1990 December (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Taste of Andrew Carnegie, 1991 May (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - New York Architecture: 1991 NYC/ AIA Design Awards/ McKim, Mead, & White’s New York, 1991 June (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - New York in Watercolor: the Landscapes of William Rickarby Miller (1818-1893), 1991 September (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - On with the Show! Circus and Theater Posters from the Collection of the New-York Historical Society (at Paine Webber Gallery), 1991 September (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Imagining the World: Columbian Iconography, 1991 November (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Imagining the World: Columbian Iconography, 1991 November (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - While They Fought: The Home Front in New York City, 1991 October (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Forever Wild: The Adirondack Experience/ Louis XIV Chair Rediscovery, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Egon Neustadt Collection of Tiffany Lamps (Permanent), 1994 April (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 19th Century Masterworks from the New-York Historical Society (at the Equitable Gallery), 1994 June (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Cole: Landscape into History/ Treasury of the Past, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Wrought from Common Clay: A Century of NY Stoneware/ Unconventional Currier & Ives/ Inventing the Skyline: The Architecture of Cass Gilbert, 1996 January, 1998 April, 2000 September (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified exhibit photos/ Loan exhibits: N-YHS Egyptian Collection at Brooklyn Museum/ Loan exhibits: Maps at Abraham and Strauss; War of 1812 at Grolier Club, Undated, 1943 February (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Loan Exhibits: Union Dime Savings Bank/ Julia Richmond High School/ Chicago Historical Society/ Franklin Society, 1948, 1949, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Loan Exhibits: A Century and a Quarter of Democratic Political History at the National Democratic Club/ Beekman Hunteriana Collection at New York Academy of Medicine/ When New York Was Young traveling exhibit/ Oppenheim Collins Department store/ B. Altman department store, 1958, 1960, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Posters: World of Washington Irving, Men and Ships of the American Navy, Knickerbocker Holiday, 1944, 1979, undated (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 3)
  - Poster: American Museum of Folk Art and New-York Historical Society exhibit, 1980-1981 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 10)
  - Poster: Grateful Dead: Now Playing at the New-York Historical Society, 2010 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 10)
  - Posters: Washingtoniana and Lincolniana, Society of Illustrators, Trinity School, 1864, 1940s - 1980s (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 12)
  - American in Daguerreotypes, 1958 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 14)
- Series III: School Programs, 1920s-1990
  The photographs in this series show various school groups taking tours, visiting exhibits, and watching plays and listening to lectures in the auditorium and the backyard.
  - Groups at N-YHS, 1920s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Groups from P.S. 44, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    The photographs in this series show various school groups at N-YHS from the 1920's through the 1990's. The student depicted are taking tours, visiting exhibits, or watching plays or listening to lectures in the auditorium or the backyard. The student appear to be from both grade school and high school.
- Series IV: Public Programs, 1864, 1987-1990
  The photographs in this series show concerts, lectures, and other general events held at N-YHS.
  - Constitution Lecture series/ NY Film Series/ Ethnic Music Festival/ Why History Matters, 1987, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Musicians and performers, 1990s, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified public events, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Photographs taken at N-YHS for other publicity purposes, 1950s-1980s (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Poster: lectures on Egypt, 1864 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 10)
- Series V: Events, 1939-1995
  This series depicts special events throughout N-YHS's history. It includes many pictures of the Strawberry Festival, an annual Spring celebration. These photos from the 1940's to the early 1970's show men and women (mostly women) dressed in their best springtime attire in the Society's garden in the backyard. The pictures from the History Maker's Gala from the 1980's depict the attendees at the fundraising event. The photographs from the St. Nicholas Day celebration show men and women enjoying a nighttime Christmas celebration at N-YHS in honor of our copy of A Visit from St. Nicholas. Other photographs from different N-YHS events are included.
  Related Archival Materials note
  Two copies of "Meeting of the New-York Historical Society in the Chapel of New York University," a print by To. Doney after a painting by J. Gollman, 1854, are located in the Portrait File, PR 52, Series II, Groups, Oversize, Clubs and Organizations, NYHS Meetings.
  - Strawberry Festival, 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1944, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1971, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Strawberry Festival, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Strawberry Festival, Undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - History Makers Gala, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - History Makers Gala, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - History Maker's Gala, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - History Maker's Gala, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - History Maker's Gala, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, 1961-1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - St. Nicholas Day Party, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Battle of Harlem Heights Centennial, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Cruise on the 330th Anniversary of the Discovery of the River by Henry Hudson, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Fire Department, 180th Birthday; Rail Return to Federal Hall, 1945, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Cruise aboard Liberte, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Belgian Tapestry Presentation; Home Show Telecase, 1953, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Sesquicentennial Tea at N-YHS; Dinner at Union Club, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Dairy Council Egg Nog Party, December 1956 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Thomas Streeter Medal Presentation, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - W. 76th Street Block Party, June 1970 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - AMNH Outdoor Community Project, September 1970 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - N-YHS 180th Birthday Gala, November 1984 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Palm Beach Party/ Wine Tasting, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Luncheon of Mayor Lindsay Staffers, Miscellaneous Events, 1995, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Strawberry Festival poster, 1944 June 12 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary dinners, 1854, 1954 (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Staff Events, 1951-1988
  This series depicts N-YHS staff members at Christmas parties, retirement parties, picnics, staff ballgames, etc.
  - Christmas Party, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Party, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Party, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Party, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Party, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Party, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Party, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Party, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Party, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Party, Maintenance Staff, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Party, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Garrett Winter retirement, 1960 October (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Edith Slattery, James Nebbergall retirements/ Sally Ryan/ Michael Sayles retirements, 1961-1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Joe Rapport retirement/ Bill Bailey, Eddie Santrucek retirements, 1971, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - N-YHS vs. Met Museum softball game, 1988 May (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940s, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Series VII: Staff, 1930s-1990s
  This series includes posed and casual shots of various staff members from the 1930's to the 1990's.
  - Directors Vail, Heslin, Bell, Hotchner/ Librarians Kelby, Wall, Mooney, Ashton, 1930s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Presidents Weekes, Zabriskie, Beekman, Olds, Goelet, Debs, 1940s-1980s (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Staff Carlson, Caulk, Dinkelaker, Evans, Green, Sciolla, Spiro, Walthins, 1930s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified staff members, Undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Series VIII: Directors and Trustees, 1940s-1980s
  This series includes formal and informal photographs of various directors and trustees from the 1940's to the 1980's.
  - Directors and Trustees Bilodean, Black, Butterfield, Gallatin, Kimball, Middendorf, Morris, Pearlstine, Prentis, Streeter, Van Alstyne, 1940s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1930s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Directors and Trustees, Undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Havemeyer, Dunlop, unidentified, 1925, 1945, undated (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Museum Images, 1960s-1990s
  This series contains images of objects in the N-YHS museum's permanent collection including items such as carriages, chairs, paintings, posters, statues, etc.
  - Advertising Posters, Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Alland Collection, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - American Revolution, 1910's-1980's (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Audubon, 1960's-1980's (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Audubon Writing Desk/Change Purse, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Bowling Green, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Carriages, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Catlin Drawings, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Chairs, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cherry Valley, NY. c. 1880-1890 (Mrs. Arther Taft Collection), Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Copley, John Singleton, Undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Crawford, Thomas (1818-1857), Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Dolls, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Durand, Asher B. (1796-1886), Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Eagles, Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - European Collection, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 4th of July, Undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Hill, John W., Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Hudson River School, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Jarvis, John Wesley (1780-1840), Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Eastman, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Lafayette, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lighting Devices, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript Material, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Maps, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Maritime, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Mary Powell (Ship & Bell), Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Needlework, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - New York City- Early Views, Not Photographs (to 1800), Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - New York City, Misc., Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New York City-Photographs, 1901-1950 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Peale, Charles Wilson, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Peale, Rembrandt, Undate (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Dutch, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Perry, Matthew C., Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Pewter Beaker (by Frederick Bassett), Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Pewterer's Flag From Procession July 13, 1788, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Portraits, 1980's-1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Pottery, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Printed Textiles, 1940's? (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Quilts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sculpture, Undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Silver, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Spinning Wheels Looms (Colonial), Undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Stieffel, Herman, Undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Stuart, Gilbert, Undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Subway, Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Trinity Church, Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Vanderlyn, John, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Victorius Volunteer, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - World War I Posters, Undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Galleries, seals, medals, 1944, undated (Drawer 12A-10)
  - Sketches for plaques and tablets, Undated (Drawer 12A-10, Folder 11)
- Series X. Architectural Plans and Drawings
  The architectural plans are housed in the oversized cabinets in Print Room storage. Some of the material in Drawers 12A-1 and 12A-8 is unfoldered.
  - York & Sawyer Architects: 13 blueprints, 1907 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 1)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: plumbing section, plan for 77th street, 1905, undated (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 2)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: eight structural blueprints, 1906 June (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 3)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: blueprint revised plan and section of entrance, 1904 September 30 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 4)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: basement framing, second, and third floor plans, 1902 May 7 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 5)
  - Carstesen (George B.) & Gildemeister (C.H.): interior and exterior painted elevations, 1854 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 6)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: plan of concrete front basement wall and footings; roof framing plan, 1901 October 25 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 7)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: plan of foundation piers, 1902 August 14 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 7)
  - Drawing showing joining of granite work of central portion (courses A through T), 1902 September 9 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 7)
  - Carstesen & Gildemeister: interior and exterior watercolor elevations and pland, [1854] (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 8)
  - York & Sawyer: linen floor plans of basement, first, second, and third floors; first, second, and third floor framing; roof framing; rear elevation; roof; front wall; foundation beams of central part of buildingcombined sections and plans; elevations of foundation piers, 1902 May 7, October 10, December 15 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 9)
  - Three blueprints, 1937 October 5 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 10)
  - Three blueprints, 1937 May 5 (Drawer 12A-1, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified floor plan sketches (basement, first, second, second mezzanine, third, fourth floors) (Drawer 12A-1)
  - Young & Sawyer Architects: blueprints of floor plans for basement, first, second, and third floors, 1925 May 15 (Drawer 12A-2, Folder 1)
  - Nygren, Tenney & Ohmes: auditorium, basement, and roof space above library plans, 1915 June 3 (Drawer 12A-2, Folder 2)
  - Nygren, Tenney & Ohmes: typed report detailing plan for alterations and additions to the ventilation system; auditorium plan detailing proposed revision of ductwork; roof plan detailing proposed fan and duct work; basement plan (Drawer 12A-2, Folder 3)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: electrical plans of basement, first, second, third floors; third floor gallery lighting plan; third floor heating and ventilation plan, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 1)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: riser diagram; first and second floor heating and ventilation plans; book stack, basement, roof electrical plans; revised supplement to third floor roof plan; shelves for various services, 1937 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 2)
  - Four traced plans, 1937 July 19, 20 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 3)
  - Chapman Metal Productions Co.: four door and window blueprints (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 4)
  - W. S. Tyler Company: blueprints for elevator cab and light fixtures, 1937 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 5)
  - Campbell Metal Window Corp.: 21 blueprints, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 6)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: heating and ventilation plans for basement, first, second, second mezzanine, third, attic floors, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 7)
  - Superior Steel Door & Trim Co., Inc.: profile of first floor trim; floor plan of special research room; 60 blueprints, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 8)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: Fire line and stand pipe system; basement drainage plan; basement plan detailing heating and ventilation; detail of house drain connections to sewers (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 9)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: rear and 76th street side elevations; plans of basement, first, second, second mezzanine, third, third mezzanine floors, 1936-1937 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 10)
  - Plan of basement (unidentified; Walker and Gillette Architects: 77th Street side, rear, Central Park West, 76th Street side elevations, 1937 February 15 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 11)
  - York & Sawyer Architects: transverse section, 1902 May 1 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 12)
  - Consolidated Edison Co. of N.Y., Inc.: layout of two bank transformer and switch vault below grade, 1937 June 28 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 13)
  - James Earle Frazer, sculptor: revision to inscriptions on second division, 1935 June 23 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 14)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: various ventilation and electrical work plans (linen), 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 15)
  - J.J. Fisher & Co., Inc.: details of skylight, snowguard, gutters and drains, 1937 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 16)
  - J.J. Fisher & Co., Inc.: gutter lining; bars and hole spacing; details of skylight, louver, skylight over central part, bar assembly, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-3, Folder 17)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: structural blueprints, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 1)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: structural plans, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 2)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: structural blueprints, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 3)
  - American Bridge Company: structural blueprints - columns, trusses, diagonals (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 4)
  - Del Turco Brothers: blueprints; Walker & Gillette basement plan for electrical work, 1937 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co.: detailed plans and structural blueprints, 1937 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 6)
  - Del Turco Brothers: mosaic floor and precast terrazzo treads, 1938 (Drawer 12A-4, Folder 7)
  - Turner Construction Co.: door diagrams; architectural and detail lists, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 1)
  - Allen Automatic Inc.: door blueprint, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Smith & Co.: registers, 1937 September - 1938 February (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 3)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: unnubmered and damawed blueprints of doors, trims, frames, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 4)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: framing plans for first floor through roof, column schedule, foundatinoplan and revisions, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 5)
  - Survey blueprints by George Hollerith, 1936-1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 6)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: schedule of wood trim - blueprints, 1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 7)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: 76th street and Central Park West elevations - whiteprints (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 8)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: heating and ventialtionplans, basement through attic - two sets, 1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 9)
  - Westinghouse Electric Elevator Co.: elevator and electrical plans - whiteprints, 1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 10)
  - American Bridge Co.: bracing plans - blueprints, 1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 11)
  - American Bridge Co.: bracing plans - whiteprints, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 12)
  - Walker & Gillette Architects: 76th street, 77th street, rear elevations - whiteprints, 1937 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 13)
  - Quaker City Iron Works: fire tank blueprints, 1937 June 23 (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 14)
  - Ernest Capelle: flagpole blueprint, [1937] (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 15)
  - Renderings of building exteriors, [1937] (Drawer 12A-5, Folder 16)
  - Philip N. Youtz, Architects: plans and blueprints for "Education Building", 1945 December 22 (Drawer 12A-6, Folder 1)
  - Castro-Blanco Piscioneri & Feder Architects: first and fourth floor plans, 1972 April (Drawer 12A-6, Folder 2)
  - Philip N. Youtz, Architects: photostats of "Education Building" plans (Drawer 12A-6, Folder 3)
  - Meter, Strong & Jones, Mechanical and Electrical Engineers: whiteprints for book stack; halon; painting,object, paper storage, 1974-1975 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 1)
  - Fire Controls, Inc.: floor layouts and riser diagrams, 1975 May 21 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 2)
  - Fourth floor lighting layout plans (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 3)
  - Robertshaw Controls Co.: valves, electric heaters, meter kit diagram, 1966 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 4)
  - Castro-Blanco Piscioneri & Feder Architects: plans for cellar, first through fourth floors, 1970-1972 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 5)
  - Moore & Hutchins Architects: roof plan, lightng plans, 1965, 1966 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 6)
  - Moore & Hutchins Architects: floor plans, duct work, mecahnical diagrams, 1965 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 7)
  - Moore & Hutchins Architects: voided first and second floor plans, 1966 January 17 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 8)
  - Meer, Strong & Jones, Mechanical and Electrical Engineers: lighting layout and plans, 1965-1966 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 9)
  - Moore & Hutchins Architects: light and power plans, 1966 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 10)
  - Safety First Product Corp.: detection system layouts for three and nine story buildings, 1973 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 11)
  - Fire Controls Incorporated: floor layout and riser plans, 1975 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 12)
  - J & J Fire Safety Corp.: riser diagram, section map, 1975 (Drawer 12A-7, Folder 13)
  - Paul Chiasson: renderings of exterior, lamp, Undated (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 1)
  - Welton Becket Associates: Tiffany Center plans, 1986 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 2)
  - Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer: residential tower elevations and floor plans, 1983-1984 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 3)
  - Unfoldered material: Allan A. Greenberg Architect - floor plans; unidentified floor plans; H. B. Fishman & Co. - roof plan, 1983, 1989, undated (Drawer 12A-8)
  - Luman reed door panel templates and copy photographs, 1989 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 4)
  - Clayton Wilson Associates: floor plans, Undated (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 5)
  - Skidmore Owings Merrill: storage plans, 1988 December (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 6)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: decorative arts and sculpture storage plans, 1989 June (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 7)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: floor plans for office renovations, 1989 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 8)
  - Facade Maintenance Design: elevations and details, 1990 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 9)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: floor plans and elevations, 1989 July 20 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 10)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: proposed plans, 1989 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 11)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: third and fourth floor plans, 1989 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 12)
  - D.M.C. Hopping Architects: Luman Reed gallery plans, 1988 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 13)
  - D.M.C. Hopping Architects: Luman Reed plans, 1987 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 14)
  - Charles Brondy & Associates Architects: museum shop plans, 1985 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 15)
  - Charles Brondy & Associates Architects: museum shop plans, 1985 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 16)
  - Welton Becket Associates: painting storage, 1986 June (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 17)
  - Morse & Harvey Architects: museum staff lounge plan, 1980 (Drawer 12A-8, Folder 18)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: building plans, 1990 June 11 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 1)
  - Richard Jansen Architect: print room plans, auditorium, third floor print room, galleries, 1990, 1992 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 2)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: museum storeplans, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 3)